#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeff-derosa-49a0a04 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Banking
Commercial Banking
Treasury Services

# Jeff DeRosa

Market Executive at JPMorgan Chase & Co.

San Francisco, California

## Summary

JP Morgan Chase & Co.'s Middle Market Banking & Specialized Industries is a Commercial Banking business located in 100+ offices across the US and Canada providing credit, cash management, capital markets and corporate finance advisory solutions to corporations, municipalities and not-for-profits.

Our local delivery model, coupled with the firm's global resources, allows us to provide clients with customized, comprehensive solutions and exceptional service. Our competitive advantages include robust international capabilities, our focus on industry specialization, and the ability to provide clients with access to world-class investment banking solutions. These key differentiators, along with our best-in-class core banking capabilities, and our dedication to personalized service, allow us to build long-term relationships with our clients.

Areas of expertise include:

- Commercial Lending, Asset-Based Lending, Real Estate Finance and Equipment Finance
- Treasury Services, Commercial Card Programs and Merchant Services
- International Banking, Trade and Receivables Finance
- Investment Banking, Foreign Exchange, Interest Rates and Commodities
- Asset Management and Retirement Services

### Experience

JPMorgan Chase & Co. 22 years

Market Executive
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Executive Director 1998 - Present (22 years)

## Education

Indiana University Bloomington Bachelor's Degree · (1993 - 1997)